List<Map<String, dynamic>> beginner = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'eat'?",
    "answer": "ate",
    "options": ["ate", "will eat", "eaten"]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the present continuous tense of 'go'?",
    "answer": "going",
    "options": ["went","going",  "gone"]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'run'?",
    "answer": "will run",
    "options": ["will run", "ran", "running"]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'drink'?",
    "answer": "have drunk",
    "options": [ "drank", "drink","have drunk"]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'sleep'?",
    "answer": "was sleeping",
    "options": ["slept","was sleeping",  "sleeping"]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'read'?",
    "answer": "read",
    "options": [ "reads","read", "reading"]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the present tense of 'write'?",
    "answer": "write",
    "options": ["write", "wrote", "written"]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'sing'?",
    "answer": "will sing",
    "options": [ "sang", "singing","will sing"]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'do'?",
    "answer": "have done",
    "options": [ "did","have done", "done"]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'eat'?",
    "answer": "was eating",
    "options": [ "ate","was eating", "eating"]
  }
];
List<Map<String, dynamic>> medium = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'speak'?",
    "answer": "spoke",
    "options": [ "speaking","spoke", "speaks"]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the present continuous tense of 'run'?",
    "answer": "is running",
    "options": [ "ran", "running","is running"]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'write'?",
    "answer": "will write",
    "options": ["will write", "wrote", "writing"]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'take'?",
    "answer": "have taken",
    "options": ["have taken", "took", "takes"]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'swim'?",
    "answer": "was swimming",
    "options": [ "swam", "swimming","was swimming"]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'think'?",
    "answer": "thought",
    "options": [ "thinks", "thinking","thought"]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the present tense of 'drive'?",
    "answer": "drive",
    "options": [ "drove","drive", "driving"]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'dance'?",
    "answer": "will dance",
    "options": ["danced","will dance",  "dancing"]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'see'?",
    "answer": "have seen",
    "options": ["have seen", "saw", "seeing"]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'drink'?",
    "answer": "was drinking",
    "options": [ "drank", "drinking","was drinking"]
  }
];
List<Map<String, dynamic>> expert = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'begin'?",
    "answer": "began",
    "options": ["began", "beginning", "begins"]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the present continuous tense of 'fly'?",
    "answer": "is flying",
    "options": ["is flying", "flew", "flies"]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'give'?",
    "answer": "will give",
    "options": [ "gave", "giving","will give"]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'fall'?",
    "answer": "have fallen",
    "options": ["fell", "falling","have fallen" ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'fall'?",
    "answer": "was falling",
    "options": ["was falling", "fell", "falling"]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'wear'?",
    "answer": "wore",
    "options": [ "wears","wore", "wearing"]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the present tense of 'lead'?",
    "answer": "lead",
    "options": ["lead", "led", "leading"]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'leave'?",
    "answer": "will leave",
    "options": [ "left","will leave", "leaving"]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'buy'?",
    "answer": "have bought",
    "options": ["have bought", "bought", "buying"]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'come'?",
    "answer": "was coming",
    "options": [ "came", "coming","was coming"]
  }
];


